

☐ (+1) 814-777-7019 | **I** feng@gatech.edu | **A** fxiao.me | **D** xiaofen9 | **D** f-xiao

Summary

First-year PhD. student at Georgia Tech. 7 years experience specializing in the security tool development and OS hacking. Obtainted 22 CVEs from widely used software. Interested in developing proactive and adversarial approaches to protect computer systems.

Project Experience

Nodejs Program Analysis and Automatic Bug Finding

Atlanta, USA Oct. 2019 - Now

GEORGIA TECH

- Discovered Hidden Property Abusing (HPA), a new security issue in Node.js ecosystem.
- Built Lynx, an automatic Nodejs bug finding framework by combining dynamic data flow tracking (Jalangi) and static syntax analysis (esprima).
- · Identified 13 previously unknown vulnerabilities from widely used nodejs modules (e.g., MongoDB, class-validator) and tested 60 of the most popular frameworks against them.

Windows Kernel Hacking

Wuhan, China

ANONYMOUS RED TEAM

Jul. 2017 - Feb. 2018

- Proposed a new kernel object hijacking method which bypassed the latest Windows Kernel Protection (valid until Feb 2018).
- Developed an ALL-patform Windows rootkit (40+ KLoC C).

Security Assessment on Android App Cryptography

Shanghai, China

SHANGHAI JIAOTONG UNIVERSITY

- Jun. 2016 Aug. 2016
- Discovered a new universal security risk shared by the majority of mobile apps, which can be exploited to forge apps' cryptographically consistent messages to abuse mobile services.
- Built a dynamic Android cryptography hook framework StupidHam to semi-automatically verified discovered bugs (https://github.com/ xiaofen9/StupidHam)
- · This new discovery honored as the most valuable vulnerability by Wooyun, the biggest bug hunting community in China.

Work Experience _____

Google WA USA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

May. 2020 - now

· Worked on virtualization security in Goolge Cloud Platform.

Penn State University

State College, USA Jun. 2018 - May. 2019

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- · Proposed SVHunter, a security assessment and vulnerability finding tool for Software-defined networking (SDN) controllers. We open sourced SVHunter at https://github.com/xiaofen9/SVHunter.
- · Discovered 18 previously unknown security risks from 4 most widely used SDN controllers using SVHunter, and 9 CVEs were assigned for discovering these vulnerabilities.
- The proposed work has been accepted to IEEE S&P'20, the top 1 security venue.

Tencent Shenzhen, China

SECURITY ENGINEER INTERN

Aug. 2017 - Sep. 2017

• Captured and mitigate one 0day attack (CVE 2017-9805) against servers of our company; found 8 high risk vulnerabilities from the products of

Honors & Awards_

CONTEST AWARDS

2017 Rank 1st in XMCTF. Xiamen, China 2017 First Prize of National Information Security Contest. Shanghai, China

2015 Rank 6th in 0CTF. Shanghai, China

Rank 2nd in BCTF. 2014 Beijing, China

HONORS

FENG XIAO · RÉSUMÉ MAY 24, 2020

2019	Chair Fellowship.	Atlanta, USA
2018	Rednor IST Fellowship.	State College, USA
2018	ACM CCS Student Travel Grant Award.	Toronto, Canada
2017	LeiJun Scholarship (Top 1 out of 310).	Wuhan, China
2016	National Scholarship (Awarded to top 0.2% undergrads nationwide)	Wuhan, China
2015	Yuanyi Scholarship.	Wuhan, China

Publication

Discovering Hidden Properties to Attack Node.js Ecosystem.

BlackHat'20

FENG XIAO, JIANWEI HUANG, YICHANG XIONG, GUANGLIANG YANG, HONG HU, GUOFEI GU, AND WENKE LEE

- · Proposed Lynx, a Node.js vulnerability finding tool that can automatically find bugs and construct exploits.
- Discovered 13 previously unknown Node.js vulnerabilities.

Unexpected Data Dependency Creation and Chaining: A New Attack to SDN.

S&P'20

FENG XIAO, JINQUAN ZHANG, JIANWEI HUANG, GUOFEI GU, DINGHAO WU, PENG LIU

- Proposed SVHunter, an automatic vulnerability detection tool for SDN controller.
- · Discovered 18 previously unknown SDN vulnerabilities.

PatternListener: Cracking Android Pattern Lock Using Acoustic Signals.

CCS'18

Man Zhou, Qian Wang, Jingxiao Yang, Qi Li, Feng Xiao, Zhibo Wang, Xiaofeng Chen.

• Discovered a new side-channel which is able to leak user inputs on Android platform.

Hacking the Brain: Customize Evil Protocol to Pwn an SDN Controller.

DEFCON'18

FENG XIAO, JIANWEI HUANG, PENG LIU.

• Discovered a previously unknown OpenFlow protocol design insecurity.

Enabling Secure Location Authentication in Drone (poster).

MobiCom'17

FENG XIAO, MAN ZHOU, YOUCHENG LIYE, JINGXIAO YANG, QIAN WANG.

· Proposed WiDrone, a multi-channel location cross-check system to mitigate GPS spoofing attacks targeted at CPS.

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology

Atlanta, USA

Ph.D. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

July. 2019 - Now

- · Working on system security with Prof. Wenke Lee.
- GPA: 4/4

Wuhan University

Wuhan, China

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Sept. 2014 - Jun. 2018

• GPA: 3.87/4

Programming languages

Natively fluent: C, Python, Java, PHP

Conversationally fluent: JavaScript, Matlab

May 24, 2020 Feng Xiao · Résumé 2